(This drama is related to specific characters, institutions, and groups It has nothing to do with the case and is purely fictitious (I hereby inform you)
(본 드라마는 특정 인물, 기관, 집단과 관련되어 있습니다. 해당 사건과 무관하며 순전히 허구입니다. (본 내용을 알려드립니다)
(Episode 4)
(4화)
"How can we forget our old friends"
"우리 옛 친구들을 어떻게 잊을 수 있겠습니까?"
"How can I not think about it in my heart?"
"어떻게 마음 속으로 생각하지 않을 수 있습니까?"
"How can we forget"
"우리가 어떻게 잊을 수 있겠습니까?"
thank you
감사합니다
please have fun
재미있게 보내주세요
"Old Friends"
"오래된 친구들"
"Friendship lasts forever"
"우정은 영원하다"
Please invite Jiang Ruzhen, a representative of the Paris Salon
파리살롱 대표 장루전(Jiang Ruzhen)을 초대해주세요
thank you
감사합니다
Thank you for your hard work today
오늘도 수고해주셔서 감사합니다
nothing
아무것도
Having said that
그렇게 말하면서
You are really awesome
당신은 정말 대단해요
Even the decoration is done by myself
장식도 직접 하더라구요
I seem to have seen my college days again That smart, confident and beautiful you
대학 시절을 다시 본 것 같아 그 똑똑하고 자신감 있고 아름다운 당신
Why do you keep praising me?
왜 자꾸만 칭찬해?
I'm old
나는 늙었다
I mean it
진심이야
You are more beautiful than anyone here today
오늘 여기 있는 누구보다 당신이 더 아름다워요
You really know how to say polite words
당신은 정말 예의바른 말을 할 줄 아는군요
But…
하지만…
How should I repay you?
어떻게 갚아야 할까요?
What's so hard about repaying me?
나한테 갚는 게 뭐가 그렇게 어려워?
have you heard this song
이 노래 들어봤어?
Why is this record here?
이 기록이 왜 여기에 있는 걸까요?
This is what I overheard
이건 내가 우연히 들은 얘기야
A favorite chanson
좋아하는 샹송
I never thought about it
나는 그것에 대해 생각해 본 적이 없다
I just asked the band to recommend me. A few chansons to create an atmosphere
방금 밴드에게 추천해달라고 부탁했어요. 분위기를 조성하기 위한 샹송 몇 곡
What a coincidence
정말 우연이군요
This is fate
이건 운명이야
Maybe it's fate
어쩌면 운명일지도 몰라
I don't even know what the lyrics mean
가사가 무슨 뜻인지도 모르겠어요
my whole life
내 평생
always waiting for you
항상 당신을 기다리고 있어요
The lyrics of this song express my feelings
이 노래의 가사는 내 감정을 표현한다.
you've always been like this
넌 항상 이랬어
I will feel very sorry for you
나는 당신에게 매우 미안할 것입니다
I seem to have drunk too much. I feel dizzy.
아무래도 술을 너무 많이 마신 것 같습니다. 현기증이 난다.
Are you feeling dizzy?
현기증이 나나요?
It's okay. You should just take a rest.
괜찮아요. 그냥 쉬세요.
very late
아주 늦었어
My son said he would go home today
아들이 오늘 집에 간다고 했어요
He should have been waiting for me for a long time
그 사람은 나를 오랫동안 기다리고 있었어야 했는데
You go back first, Brother Zhongzhong
먼저 돌아가세요 종중 형제님
Team Leader Wu will send you back
우 팀장이 당신을 돌려 보낼 것입니다
are you ok
괜찮아?
Yeah
응
Although it is a belated greeting
뒤늦은 인사이긴 하지만
But congratulations on your successful store opening event
하지만 성공적인 매장 오픈 이벤트를 축하드립니다
It's all thanks to the team leader
다 팀장님 덕분이에요
And about records
그리고 기록에 대해서
thank you very much
정말 고마워요
you're welcome
천만에요
That's a song the deputy commander often listens to
부사령관이 자주 듣는 노래죠
Can I listen with Ms. Jiang?
Ms. Jiang과 함께 들어도 될까요?
Isn't it better?
더 좋지 않나요?
I just want to thank you for asking me
그냥 물어봐줘서 고마워요
Did you two listen together?
둘이 같이 들었어?
Yes
예
Right
오른쪽
Please never tell the deputy chief I asked you about this
절대 부장에게 말하지 마세요. 이것저것 물어봤는데
What's wrong with this
이게 무슨 문제야?
to you
당신에게
Although not much
많지는 않지만
But this is what I want
하지만 내가 원하는 건 바로 이것이다
No need
필요 없음
I will be scolded by the deputy commander
부사령관한테 혼나겠다
I hope you will assist the deputy chief well in the future. Just given to you
앞으로도 부실장님을 잘 도와주시길 바랍니다. 방금 당신에게 주어진
you can accept it
너는 그것을 받아들일 수 있다
thank you
감사합니다
You worked hard today
오늘도 수고하셨어요
No. Thank you for helping me so much.
아니요. 많은 도움을 주셔서 감사합니다.
Go in and have a rest.
들어가서 쉬세요.
good
좋아
Mom
엄마
Why did you come back so late?
왜 이렇게 늦게 돌아왔나요?
Who is that?
그 사람은 누구입니까?
Yeah, the person who helps mom in the store
응, 가게에서 엄마 도와주는 사람
Son, let's go in quickly
아들아 빨리 들어가자
Mom is in a good mood today
엄마 오늘 기분이 좋아
You have a drink with me
나랑 한잔해요
I really want to drink with you
정말 너랑 술 마시고 싶어
but i have to go
하지만 난 가야 해
Because I have an exam starting tomorrow
내일부터 시험이니까
your first time home Going back so soon
집에 처음 왔어 너무 빨리 돌아가서
I will come back often in the future, really
앞으로 자주 올게요 정말
son
아들
You know mom only has you now, right?
엄마는 이제 너밖에 없는 거 알지?
If someone dares to hinder your future
누군가 감히 당신의 미래를 방해한다면
Even if my mother is shattered to pieces I will also help you get rid of that person
엄마가 산산조각이 나더라도 나도 그 사람 없애는 걸 도와줄게
So son
그러니까 아들아
you can't let me down
넌 날 실망시킬 수 없어
You must take the exam for senior civil servants
고위공무원 시험을 치뤄야 합니다.
don't worry
걱정하지 마세요
Mom, I will never let you down
엄마, 난 절대 당신을 실망시키지 않을 거예요
I also want to be a powerful person
나도 강한 사람이 되고 싶다
Why is my son so good?
우리 아들은 왜 이렇게 착할까요?
I sent her back
나는 그녀를 돌려보냈다
But…
하지만…
Cui Zhexiong is also at home
Cui Zhexiong도 집에 있어요
He probably didn't recognize me
그 사람은 아마 날 알아보지 못했을 거야
But...
하지만...
If I let Ms. Jiang know in the future
앞으로 장씨에게 알리면
Cui Zhexiong’s matter is related to you...
Cui Zhexiong의 문제는 당신과 관련이 있습니다 ...
Doesn't that matter?
그건 중요하지 않나요?
She can never know in her life
그녀는 인생에서 결코 알 수 없습니다
home run
홈런
home run…
홈런…
boss
보스
walk slowly
천천히 걷다
(All sold out)
(모두 매진)
(Refuse to buy scalper tickets)
(스캘퍼 티켓 구매를 거부합니다)
Uncle, I have a ticket here
삼촌, 나 여기 티켓 있어요
30,000 won per piece
개당 30,000원
What?
무엇?
It's already the second half of the second game.
벌써 2차전 후반전이다.
Deduct the money from the first game
첫 번째 게임에서 돈을 공제
25,000 won
25,000원
OK 27,000 won
OK 27,000원
good
좋아
Hyung Soo
형수
3 tickets worth 27,000 won
27,000원 상당의 티켓 3장
The second round is about to end
2라운드가 끝나가네요
Okay…
알았어…
take it
가져가
I wish you a happy watching football
즐거운 축구관전 되시기 바랍니다
Come on
어서
Let's go watch football
축구 보러 가자
Let's go
가자
Give them 3 tickets
티켓 3장 주세요
How much does one cost?
하나의 비용은 얼마입니까?
10,000 won
10,000원
Total 30,000 won
총 30,000원
You kid is really...
너 꼬마는 정말...
Hello
안녕하세요
We have no cost
우리는 비용이 들지 않습니다
These are the tickets we queued up for last night
이건 우리가 어젯밤에 대기한 티켓이야
Really
정말로
We don't want to sell it, just go away
우리는 그것을 팔고 싶지 않습니다. 그냥 가십시오.
He has promised to sell it to me for 10,000 How can anyone be like this?
그는 그것을 나에게 10,000에 팔겠다고 약속했습니다 어떻게 사람이 이럴 수 있니?
what
뭐
That's how I am
나는 그래요
Don't make me angry
나를 화나게 하지 마세요
Just listen to the radio, you know?
라디오만 들어봐, 알지?
Sorry
미안
Wait
잠깐
I'll sell you the tickets
티켓 팔게요
thank you
감사합니다
Say thank you quickly
빨리 고맙다고 말하세요
I wish you a happy watching football game
행복한 축구 경기 관람하시길 바랍니다
Do the kids want to watch the game?
아이들이 경기를 보고 싶어하나요?
Are all the tickets sold out?
티켓이 모두 매진됐나요?
Only one left
하나만 남았습니다
one piece
원피스
Can you give me the remaining one for free?
남은 한 개는 무료로 주실 수 있나요?
Which brat is it again...
또 무슨 새끼야...
it's me
나야
Li Douxue it's you
리두수에 너야
You scared us, brat.
우리를 겁주었잖아, 새끼야.
Brother
형제
Brother Xuanyu
쉬안위 형제
Li Douxue
리두수에
Why are you selling scalper tickets?
스캘퍼 티켓을 판매하는 이유는 무엇인가요?
You are much thinner
훨씬 말랐잖아
i got fat
나 뚱뚱해졌어
Come…
오세요…
I heard you were released from prison when I went to visit you.
내가 당신을 만나러 갔을 때 당신이 감옥에서 풀려났다는 소식을 들었습니다.
sorry
미안
But you came to us now, you brat?
그런데 이제 우리한테 왔잖아, 이 새끼야?
You are obviously very happy
당신은 분명히 매우 행복합니다
Come to Xuanyu
쉬안위로 오세요
By the way, have you heard about Yong Pil?
그런데 혹시 용필에 대해 들어보셨나요?
that guy
그 사람
what are you doing now
지금 뭐해?
in our constituency MPs who work for the country
우리 선거구에서 나라를 위해 일하는 국회의원들
(2 years ago Gwangju Prison) I feel that the state’s sentence for money order fraud is too light
(2년 전 광주교도소) 나는 우편환 사기에 대한 주정부의 형량이 너무 가볍다고 생각합니다.
MPs hope they can last a lifetime
의원들은 평생 지속될 수 있기를 바랍니다
Can't hold the spoon
숟가락을 잡을 수 없다
The old man you are loyal to is not a congressman.
당신이 충성하는 노인은 국회의원이 아니다.
He is the scum of the world and an unscrupulous boss
그는 세상의 쓰레기이고 파렴치한 상사입니다
I…
나는…
don't know that person
그 사람을 몰라
Of course you don't know him
물론 당신은 그 사람을 모르죠
That building in Cheonan that you used to defraud
네가 사취하던 천안 그 빌딩
It's his sister-in-law's building
그 사람의 처제 건물이에요
I don't know
모르겠어요
I really don't know
난 정말 모르겠어요
i was wrong
내가 틀렸어
Let's get started
시작하자
Don't do this
이러지 마세요
Take it quickly
빨리 가져가
i can't do it
난 할 수 없어
I can't do it either
나도 할 수 없어
Hey brat
안녕 개자식
There's going to be a night patrol soon.
곧 야간 순찰이 있을 예정이에요.
what are you doing here
여기서 뭐해?
who is this guy
이 사람은 누구입니까?
People who share the same room with them
같은 방을 쓰는 사람들
children
어린이
are you calling me
나한테 전화하는 거야?
What are you doing here?
여기서 뭐하는거야?
Oh my god
맙소사
Don't move at all
전혀 움직이지 마세요
boy
소년
You don't know who I am?
내가 누군지 모르시나요?
I think you don’t want to live anymore
내 생각에는 당신이 더 이상 살고 싶지 않은 것 같아요
You don’t know who I am either, right?
너도 내가 누군지 모르지?
I had no intention of living in the first place
원래 살 생각은 없었는데
If you don't let me go
만약 당신이 나를 놓아주지 않는다면
I don't know what I'll do to you
내가 당신에게 무슨 짓을 할지 모르겠어요
Really?
정말요?
Whatever you want
당신이 원하는 무엇이든
Looks like we want to live together
같이 살고 싶은 것 같은데
Still have to die together
그래도 같이 죽어야지
what are you doing
뭐하는거야?
What are you doing?
뭐하는 거야?
Don't move
움직이지 마세요
Be careful I'll kill you...
조심해 죽여버릴거야...
Hello me...
안녕 나...
I'll cut you into pieces
널 조각조각 잘라버릴 거야
Xuanyu
쉬안위
do you really want to die
너 정말 죽고 싶니?
When have you ever seen me holding a knife?
내가 칼 들고 있는 걸 언제 본 적 있어?
No?
아니요?
Of course not
물론 아니지
You tell him
당신이 그에게 말해요
Please act more handsomely Yes
좀 더 멋있게 행동해주세요 예
More handsome?
더 잘생겼나요?
You act again
또 행동하네
Be careful I'll kill you...
조심해 죽여버릴거야...
Just say I don’t hold a knife anymore
이제 칼은 안 든다고 해
Douxue, you suffered a lot because of Yongbi.
두수씨, 용비 때문에 고생이 많으셨어요.
The average person goes into the solitary room once He will become good immediately
보통 사람은 독방에 한 번 들어가요. 그는 즉시 좋아질 것이다
But you were imprisoned four times
하지만 당신은 네 번이나 감옥에 갇혔어요
You are probably the first person in the history of the Ministry of Justice, right?
아마 법무부 역사상 최초의 인물이겠죠?
Yes
예
I'm in solitary confinement
나는 독방에 갇혀 있다
I finally understand why prison is a school
감옥이 학교인 이유를 드디어 이해했다
The world is so dangerous
세상은 너무 위험해
You can never learn by studying
공부로는 절대 배울 수 없다
That's right
그렇죠
You're a rookie
당신은 신인이에요
When did you start training?
훈련은 언제 시작했나요?
I am now a five-star general
나는 이제 5성 장군이다
right
맞아
Yes that's right
네 그렇죠
Come and raise a glass
와서 잔을 들어
To the five-star general
오성 장군에게
Cheers
건배
I've been waiting for a long time
나는 오랫동안 기다려 왔습니다.
I'm afraid auntie will change her mind
이모가 마음을 바꿀까봐 걱정이에요
Got the luggage right away
바로 짐을 챙겨서
Hey, you can't put away unwashed clothes Bring it too
야, 빨래 안한 옷은 버리면 안 돼 그것도 가져와
You wash and wear it here
여기서 세탁하고 입으세요
what
뭐
"Things that are past"
"지난 일들"
"Even if you try hard to save it"
"구하려고 애써도"
"tears of sadness flow"
"슬픔의 눈물이 흐른다"
what are you doing
뭐하는거야?
You…
당신은…
Aren't you afraid of me?
당신은 나를 두려워하지 않습니까?
Afraid but...
두렵지만...
you are beautiful
당신은 아름답습니다
"Dark eyes like starlight"
"별빛처럼 검은 눈"
(Sun Film Company Land Registration Certificate)
(썬필름사 토지등록증)
Have you heard of Sun Films?
썬필름(Sun Films)에 대해 들어보셨나요?
Their office is right here
그 사무실이 바로 여기 있어요
drive carefully
조심해서 운전해
good
좋아
Walk slowly, brother
천천히 걸어요 형님
The owner seems to believe you
주인이 당신을 믿는 것 같아요
Of course I believe it
물론 나는 그것을 믿는다.
So tired…
너무 피곤해…
What's wrong with you, brat?
무슨 문제 있어?
If Busan accounts for 20% of the distribution market What about Seoul and Gyeonggi-do?
부산이 유통시장의 20%를 차지한다면 서울과 경기도는 어떤가요?
Including the small copyright market Seoul accounts for 33%
소규모 저작권 시장 포함 서울은 33%
Gyeonggi Province and Gangwon Province The total should account for 15%
경기도, 강원도 총계는 15%를 차지해야 합니다.
But if you want to enter the Jingjiang area
하지만 Jingjiang 지역에 들어가고 싶다면
You have to target the Central Publishing Company
중앙 출판사를 타겟팅해야 합니다.
You might have to risk your life
목숨을 걸어야 할 수도 있다
Central Distribution Company?
중앙 유통 회사?
(College Music Festival award-winning singer Shin Bo-yeon)
(대학가요제 수상가수 신보연)
let's drink
마시자
Now?
지금?
My boss wants me to only sing during the daytime
상사가 낮에만 노래 부르길 원해요
He said the guests tonight didn't like it
오늘 밤 손님들이 마음에 안 든다고 하더군요
Dad
아빠
Am I useless?
나는 쓸모 없는 걸까?
Can't even hold on to a small theater
작은 극장도 버틸 수 없어
But you don't have to worry
하지만 걱정할 필요는 없어요
I will definitely buy back our theater
나는 우리 극장을 꼭 다시 사겠습니다
I miss you so much dad
아빠가 너무 그리워요
And mom
그리고 엄마
(Sender: Wu Dingchen) (Recipient: Li Douxue, letter returned)
(발신자: 우딩첸) (수신자: Li Douxue, 편지 반송)
Hello Li Douxue
안녕하세요 리두수에
How are you doing, kid?
잘 지내요?
are you out of jail
너 감옥에서 나왔니?
You should be out of jail
넌 감옥에서 나가야 해
Also
또한
Instead of seeing the other person living a useless life
상대방이 쓸모없는 삶을 사는 모습을 보기보다
It's better to break up
헤어지는 게 낫지
we are well divided
우리는 잘 나뉘어져 있어
please let go
제발 놓아주세요
Still free
아직 무료
what
뭐
I thought as time passed She will slowly forget you
시간이 지날수록 생각났어 그녀는 천천히 당신을 잊을 것입니다
I think you guys should break up
내 생각엔 너희들 헤어져야 할 것 같아
This is my last wish
이게 내 마지막 소원이야
please help me
제발 도와주세요
Douxue
두쉬
Really
정말로
Where have you been and only now are you back?
어디 계셨다가 이제서야 돌아오셨나요?
Brother Feng Hao was taken away
Feng Hao 형제가 끌려갔습니다.
what
뭐
Which police station is he at?
그 사람은 어느 경찰서에 있어요?
If it's the police
경찰이라면
You can also buy it with money
돈으로도 살 수 있어요
He was captured by Guangzhuo
그는 광주에서 포로로 잡혔다.
That kid because of what happened before Always holding a grudge
그 아이는 예전에 있었던 일 때문에 늘 원한을 품고
I'm not telling you to stay with Brother Feng Hao
나는 당신에게 Feng Hao 형제와 함께 있으라고 말하는 것이 아닙니다.
sorry
미안
Douxue
두쉬
They want you to go there alone
그들은 당신이 거기 혼자 가길 원해요
what to do
무엇을 해야할지
Absolutely not
절대 아니다
If you go, you will die, Dou Xue
가면 죽는다, 두설
They just haven't expanded their sphere of influence yet.
그들은 아직 영향력의 영역을 확장하지 않았습니다.
You didn’t know that Kwang Tak Gang is in Seoul Is it one of the top five gangs?
광탁강이 서울에 있다는 걸 몰랐지? 상위 5개 갱단 중 하나인가요?
I know you are very loyal
나는 당신이 매우 충실하다는 것을 알고 있습니다
But if you go like this, you are asking for death.
하지만 이대로 가면 죽음을 요구하는 셈이다.
Hello Xuanyu
안녕하세요 쉬안위
what do you think
어떻게 생각하세요?
I don't care
난 상관없어
As long as you are here
당신이 여기 있는 한
Hey, there are so many of them
이야, 너무 많아
And not with bare hands
그리고 맨손이 아닌
Will bring guys with me
남자들 데리고 갈게
Whether it's a surprise attack or a head-on battle
기습이든 정면 대결이든
Even that...
그것마저도...
By the way, even Bruce Lee and Jackie Chan It’s also hard to come back alive
그런데 Bruce Lee와 Jackie Chan조차도 살아서 돌아오는 것도 힘들어
It doesn't matter
그것은 중요하지 않습니다
I just need to defeat Guangzhuo
그냥 광주를 이겨야지
Hey, is it time to clean now?
자, 이제 청소할 시간인가요?
Douxue
두쉬
Are you writing the Three Kingdoms?
삼국지를 쓰시나요?
Is it enough for the leader to compete in a one-on-one battle?
리더가 일대일 전투를 벌이는 것만으로도 충분합니까?
Do you think those people are in the underworld? So elegant and noble
그 사람들이 지하세계에 있다고 생각하시나요? 너무 우아하고 고귀해요
What else should I do?
또 무엇을 해야 합니까?
I can't leave Brother Feng Hao alone.
나는 Feng Hao 형제를 내버려 둘 수 없습니다.
Surrender
항복
what
뭐
I heard that Lian Guangzhuo is a very loyal person
Lian Guangzhuo가 매우 충성스러운 사람이라고 들었습니다.
You went alone to save Brother Feng Hao
당신은 Feng Hao 형제를 구하기 위해 혼자 갔습니까?
He might accept your surrender
그 사람이 당신의 항복을 받아들일 수도 있어요
Surrender?
항복?
You have to fight to save the prison at the same time
동시에 감옥을 구하기 위해 싸워야 합니다
Are you going to be Lian Guangzhuo's younger brother?
Lian Guangzhuo의 남동생이 될 건가요?
If he wants to be successful, he can definitely become famous.
성공하고 싶다면 반드시 유명해질 수 있다.
Just don't be a little brother
그냥 동생처럼 굴지 마
What else can I do if I am not my younger brother?
내가 동생이 아니면 또 무엇을 할 수 있겠는가?
he's coming
그 사람이 온다
The one who can fight very well...
정말 잘 싸울 수 있는 사람..
Look who's here. Long time no see.
여기 누가 왔는지 보세요. 오랜만이에요.
Liu Yongbi
유용비
Do you remember that I was in jail? What did I say to you?
내가 감옥에 있던 것을 기억하시나요? 내가 당신에게 뭐라고 말했습니까?
I won't let you live
널 살려두지 않을 거야
You can still laugh
아직도 웃을 수 있어요
It was your elder brother who came to see me today
오늘 나를 만나러 온 사람은 네 형이었어.
Stop making trouble
문제를 일으키지 마세요
people brought
사람들이 데려왔어
Douxue
두쉬
My name is Li Douxue
내 이름은 리두수(Li Douxue)입니다.
You stand out
당신은 눈에 띕니다
Became the boss of the Land King at the age of 25
25세에 대지왕의 보스가 되다
What boss...
무슨 상사...
Aren't you our boss?
당신은 우리 상사 아닌가요?
What? Aren’t you the boss?
무엇? 당신이 사장이 아니신가요?
I should...
나는 ...
That's right, hmm...
그렇죠, 흠...
Brother Feng Hao is following me
Feng Hao 형제가 나를 팔로우하고 있습니다.
We grew up together like brothers in an orphanage.
우리는 고아원의 형제처럼 함께 자랐습니다.
Originally, I would even share a bean.
원래는 콩도 나눠먹을 예정이었는데.
Will make money now He treats me like a stranger
이제 돈 벌겠다 그 사람은 나를 낯선 사람처럼 대해요
what do you think
어떻게 생각하세요?
You are the boss. Tell me.
당신은 상사입니다. 말해 주세요.
A bean can be eaten separately
콩은 따로 먹어도 되고
But it's absolutely impossible to divide a bag of beans
하지만 콩 한 봉지를 나누는 건 절대 불가능해요
this is human nature
이것이 인간의 본성이다
Really?
정말요?
So inhumane
너무 비인간적이야
Then you are the boss, you should be responsible, right?
그럼 당신이 사장이니까 책임을 져야겠죠?
However
그러나
I don't want to live so mean
난 그렇게 못되게 살고 싶지 않아
that bag of beans
그 콩 한 봉지
Let's share it together
함께 공유해요
From now on we will be a family
이제부터 우리는 가족이 될 거예요
What a family
정말 가족이에요
Big brother
형님
Xuanyu
쉬안위
Brat, you took the wrong medicine
형, 약을 잘못 먹었어요
How is it
어때요?
Do you want to treat us as a family?
우리를 가족처럼 대하고 싶나요?
That was the four of us yesterday Half the money you make selling ticket scalpers at the ballpark.
어제 우리 넷이 그랬어 야구장에서 티켓 암표 판매원을 팔아 버는 돈의 절반.
Recently, because of the strict control
최근에는 엄격한 통제로 인해
So business is not very good
그래서 장사가 별로 안 좋아요
You are so courageous. You are very talented...
당신은 정말 용기가 있습니다. 당신은 매우 재능이 있습니다 ...
come have a drink
한 잔 하러 오세요
But I heard that you will never bow to others
하지만 남에게 절대 절을 안 한다고 들었는데
I heard that you never bowed your head to Yong Pil in prison.
감옥에서 용필에게 한번도 고개를 숙인 적이 없다고 들었습니다.
But why did you suddenly bow your head in front of me?
그런데 왜 갑자기 내 앞에서 고개를 숙였나요?
Do you want me to guess?
제가 추측해 볼까요?
This sentence is very popular among young people recently
이 문장은 최근 젊은이들 사이에서 매우 인기가 높습니다.
Keep friends by your side
친구들을 옆에 두세요
The enemy must be inseparable
적군은 분리될 수 없어야 한다
It is easiest to betray those around you
주변 사람을 배신하는 것이 가장 쉽습니다
This is called a coup
이것을 쿠데타라고 한다
Have you heard of the coup?
쿠데타 소식을 들어보셨나요?
Are you trying to destroy my gang?
내 갱단을 파괴하려는 겁니까?
Say it
말해봐
Right?
그렇죠?
was discovered
발견되었다
You are so observant
당신은 관찰력이 뛰어나군요
Yongbi
용비
You kid...
너 꼬마야...
What are you still doing?
아직도 뭐하고 있어요?
Come here quickly
빨리 여기로 와
Just in case…
혹시라도…
They won't let me surrender
그들은 내가 항복하는 걸 허락하지 않을 거야
This is the last time students
이번이 마지막이에요 학생들
During a protest near a baseball stadium The tear gas I picked up
야구장 인근 시위 중 내가 주운 최루탄
You should be able to run away with this
이걸로 도망칠 수 있어야 해
Are there towels?
수건은 있나요?
Get away, brat
저리 가, 새끼야
Did you think you were going to kill me? It'll be fine
나를 죽일 거라고 생각했나요? 괜찮을 거야
My boys will chase you To the ends of the earth
내 친구들이 당신을 쫓아갈 거예요 땅끝까지
we won't do anything to you
우리는 너한테 아무 짓도 안 할 거야
Even if you let me go now, you won't be able to survive.
지금 나를 놓아준다고 해도 넌 살아남을 수 없을 거야.
So you'd better kill me now
그러니 지금 나를 죽이는 게 좋을 거야
I say it again
다시한번 말하지만
I won't die and we won't kill you
나는 죽지 않을 것이고 우리는 당신을 죽이지 않을 것이다
What do you want?
당신은 무엇을 원하세요?
It’s already overflowing and it’s hard to recover
이미 넘쳐서 회복하기 힘들어
Even if the water spills out
물이 쏟아져도
As long as the cup is not broken
컵이 깨지지 않는 한
Just put it back in
그냥 다시 넣으세요
Big brother
형님
Kneel down quickly
빨리 무릎꿇어
Really
정말로
Brother, the cup is not broken yet
형님, 컵은 아직 깨지지 않았어요
We are willing to be your water
우리는 당신의 물이 될 의향이 있습니다
Stop playing tricks, you brat.
장난 좀 그만 쳐, 이 새끼야.
I mean it
진심이야
As long as you are willing to accept us
당신이 우리를 기꺼이 받아들이는 한
We can hand over the land king Half of the income is given to you
우리는 땅의 왕을 넘겨줄 수 있습니다 수입의 절반이 당신에게 주어집니다
what do you want to do
너는 무엇을 하고 싶니?
I know you are very ambitious
나는 당신이 매우 야심적이라는 것을 알고 있습니다
You won’t be content with staying in Muqiaodong, right?
무교동에 머무르는 것만으로는 만족하지 못하시겠죠?
To dominate Myeongdong and Seoul
명동과 서울을 장악하다
You need men like me
나 같은 남자가 필요해
I need...
나는 필요하다...
Bosses and organizations like you
당신과 같은 상사와 조직
What do you mean...I am Liu Bei
무슨 말이야...나는 유비다
Are you...Zhao Zilong?
당신은...자오쯔룽?
You can think whatever you want
당신은 당신이 원하는대로 생각할 수 있습니다
Very good
아주 좋음
But…
하지만…
How can I trust that you won't betray me?
당신이 나를 배신하지 않을 것이라고 어떻게 믿을 수 있습니까?
I always need some guarantee, right?
나는 항상 보증이 필요합니다. 그렇죠?
If you need guarantee That's the deal. We're no longer a family.
보증이 필요한 경우 그게 거래입니다. 우리는 더 이상 가족이 아닙니다.
Because no matter what guarantee I put out
왜냐면 내가 어떤 보장을 내놔도
You will doubt me
당신은 나를 의심할 것이다
ok
알았어
Then we...
그러면 우리는...
Just find someone else
그냥 다른 사람 찾아보세요
Please walk carefully and slowly
조심해서 천천히 걸어주세요
Then come to Taoyuan to have a romantic relationship.
그렇다면 타오위안으로 오셔서 연애를 해보세요.
Let's just be a family, brat
그냥 가족이 되자, 얘야
give me a cigarette
담배 좀 줘
How is it
어때요?
Have you done your homework well during this time?
그동안 숙제는 잘 했나요?
boss
보스
Do you want to make more money?
더 많은 돈을 벌고 싶나요?
But Gwangju market only accounts for 10% of the entire market
하지만 광주시장은 전체 시장의 10%에 불과하다.
Movie companies can only make so much money
영화사는 돈을 많이 벌 수 있다
Just stop showing off.
그만 과시하세요.
We…
우리는…
Let’s attack the Gyeonggi-do market
경기도시장을 공략하자
what
뭐
Two or three years ago, Gyeonggi Province and Gangwon Province Only accounts for 15% of the total market
2~3년 전 경기도와 강원도 전체 시장의 15%만을 차지
But as satellite cities in the metropolitan area rapid increase
하지만 수도권의 위성도시로서 급격한 증가
The market has become bigger
시장이 더 커졌다
Very potential to make money
돈을 벌 가능성이 매우 높음
what are you talking about
무슨 소리 하는 거야?
You can't do things like this in this circle
이 서클에서는 이런 일을 할 수 없습니다
Taking someone's territory will get you into trouble
누군가의 영토를 빼앗으면 문제가 생길 것입니다
You might be hacked with a knife
칼로 해킹당할 수도 있어요
Markets in Gyeonggi-do and Gangwon-do
경기도와 강원도의 시장
has been divided among three film companies
3개 영화사로 분할되어
How do we get in?
어떻게 들어가나요?
Break the triangle structure
삼각형 구조를 깨뜨려라
squeeze out a company
회사를 짜내다
replaced by us
우리로 대체
What can you do
당신은 무엇을 할 수 있나요
Think of a way from now on
이제부터 방법을 생각해 보세요
But if I can really do it
하지만 내가 정말 할 수 있다면
can you give me shares
나한테 주식 좀 줄래?
Look at you vixen
너 좀 봐 암여우야
OK, give it a try
좋아요, 한번 시도해 보세요
If it can be successful, let alone shares
성공할 수 있다면 공유는 커녕
You want me to marry you
당신은 내가 당신과 결혼하기를 원해요
Really?
정말요?
You must abide by the agreement
계약을 준수해야 합니다.
You girl have already thought about it, right?
당신은 이미 그것에 대해 생각하고 있었죠?
good
좋아
You give it a try
한번 시도해 보세요
old…boss
늙었어…보스
How many shares does Brother Guang Zhuo hold?
Guang Zhuo 형제는 몇 주를 보유하고 있습니까?
He didn't invest at all
그는 전혀 투자하지 않았다
I got 30% just for helping with management.
경영에 도움을 준 대가로 30%를 받았습니다.
30% What a robber
30% 정말 도둑이군요
If you spend your own money eating, drinking and having sex What kind of gangster is he?
자기 돈으로 먹고 마시고 섹스하면 그는 어떤 종류의 갱스터입니까?
But I remember their account books were in a mess
하지만 그 사람들의 장부가 엉망이었던 걸 기억해요
Not to mention turnover
매출액은 말할 것도 없고
Yong Pil and the liquor wholesaler he manages I made two sets of accounts and smuggled my drinking money.
용필과 그가 경영하는 주류도매상 계좌를 두 개 만들어서 술값을 밀반입했어요.
Why on earth did Big Brother want to absorb that kid?
도대체 빅 브라더는 왜 그 아이를 흡수하고 싶어했을까요?
I really can't understand
정말 이해할 수가 없어요
If you want him to come in to enhance your fighting power,
전투력을 강화하기 위해 그가 들어오길 원한다면,
Then why should he be equal to Yongbi brother?
그렇다면 왜 용비 형과 동등해야 하는가?
Brother, am I wrong?
형님, 제가 틀렸나요?
You guys are really
너희들은 정말
It makes me lose my appetite
식욕을 잃게 만드네요
sorry
미안
Brother, I'm sorry
형님, 미안해요
Is this some kind of soup restaurant?
일종의 수프 전문점인가요?
Alas, in a high-end hotel It tastes like rice soup and pickled radish
아아 고급호텔에서 국밥 맛과 단무지 맛이 나네요
Of course guests won't come to your door
물론 손님은 집에 오지 않을 것입니다.
I know that big brother has left you in charge of this place.
나는 큰 형이 당신에게 이곳을 맡겼다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
But I must have lunch here have another cup of coffee
하지만 여기서 점심을 먹어야 해 커피 한잔 더 마셔
You won’t have indigestion
소화불량은 없을 거에요
If you have indigestion I will buy you gastrointestinal medicine
소화불량인 경우 위장약 사줄게
From now on, only order what is on the menu
이제부터는 메뉴에 있는 것만 주문하세요
Don't forget to pay
지불하는 것을 잊지 마세요
You brat...
이 녀석...
Let's go after drinking coffee
커피 마시고 가자
I'll treat you to this meal today
오늘은 이 식사로 대접할게
After all, we are a family
결국 우리는 가족이에요
Still a family...
그래도 가족이네...
I don't think we are a family
내 생각엔 우리는 가족이 아닌 것 같아
Be careful
조심하세요
We coexist peacefully
우리는 평화롭게 공존해요
I'll be nice to you
잘해줄게
Let's go
가자
The food here must be delicious
여기 음식은 맛있을 거에요
Hello, Boss Yin
안녕하세요, 이진보스님
Me? I'm working
나? 나는 일하고 있어요
why
왜
what did you say
뭐라고 했어?
Why are you so embarrassed? You always ask me to send my little brother over for that kind of thing
왜 그렇게 당황스러워요? 넌 항상 나한테 그런 일 때문에 내 남동생을 보내달라고 하네
what did you say
뭐라고 했어?
Got it
알았어요
Then you should also take care of our little brother.
그렇다면 당신도 우리 남동생을 돌봐야 합니다.
And…
그리고…
After you finish filming, bring an actress here
촬영 끝나면 여기로 배우 데려오세요
That's right
그렇죠
Just follow the flow and arrange the banquet.
그냥 흐름을 따라 연회를 준비하세요.
Lunzi and Wild Wolf
Lunzi와 야생 늑대
This is a gift from big brother to you
이건 형이 너에게 주는 선물이야
If you need anything, you can tell me anytime.
필요한 것이 있으면 언제든지 말씀해 주세요.
Thank you bro
고마워요 형
I'll keep it short.
짧게 말하겠습니다.
From now on, don't worry about each other anymore
이제부터 더 이상 서로 걱정하지 마세요.
The whole family just wants to eat and drink together Fighting side by side, do you understand?
온 가족이 함께 먹고 마시고 싶어 나란히 싸우는 것, 이해합니까?
Yes eldest brother
응 큰 형님
Everyone raises a toast
모두들 건배해요
Cheers
건배
I get it. Okay...
알겠습니다. 알았어...
Really
정말로
Hey, where is Douxue now?
안녕하세요, Douxue는 지금 어디에 있나요?
(Sun Pictures)
(선픽쳐스)
Really…
정말…
(Planning Office)
(기획실)
I know
알아요
minister I heard that the filming schedule has been delayed a lot
장관 촬영 일정이 많이 늦어졌다고 들었어요
Will the movie be released in time?
영화가 제때 개봉되나요?
These guys are waiting to die.
이 사람들은 죽기를 기다리고 있습니다.
I'll take care of this matter
이 문제는 내가 처리할게
Don't interfere, got it?
방해하지 마세요, 알겠죠?
Minister, where are you going?
장관님, 어디 가시나요?
Open the sinner's mouth and feed him poison
죄인의 입을 열어 독약을 먹이라
Yes
예
Empress…
황후…
drink it
마셔라
Is what she is drinking really poison?
그녀가 마시고 있는 것은 정말 독인가?
That's Shuanghetang
그게 솽허탕이에요
It turns out to be Shuanghetang. It’s really dangerous.
Shuanghetang으로 밝혀졌습니다. 정말 위험해요.
Empress…
황후…
But in the hands of Shang Gong Looks like he's wearing a watch
하지만 Shang Gong의 손에 시계를 차고 있는 것 같네요
That's so funny
그거 참 웃긴데
card
카드
Damn...
젠장...
Hello
안녕하세요
What's wrong
무슨 일이야?
What is this Wait a moment...
이것은 무엇입니까? 잠깐만요...
who are you
당신은 누구입니까?
director
감독
Wait, help me hold up my headgear.
잠깐만요, 모자 쓰는 걸 도와주세요.
What's wrong? Is it NG?
무슨 일이야? NG인가요?
So brilliant
너무 훌륭해
Miss Song Yanzhu
송옌주 선생님
Hottest male directors of the 21st century
21세기 가장 핫한 남성 감독
He has been waiting for you for a long time
그 사람은 오랫동안 당신을 기다리고 있었어요
Come out quickly
빨리 나와라
They are actress Song Yeon-joo Someone sent from another movie crew
배우 송연주 입니다 다른 영화 제작진이 보낸 누군가
Hey, tell the director to keep waiting.
아, 감독님한테 계속 기다리라고 전해주세요.
We must today Just finish filming this scene
오늘은 우리가 해야 할 일 이 장면만 찍으면 끝
Clear the place quickly
빨리 자리를 비워라
If I count to three and you still don’t get out of the way...
셋까지 세어도 네가 아직도 비켜주지 않으면...
Just don't blame me for taking action
조치를 취했다고 해서 나를 비난하지 마세요.
You... just do it
너...그냥 해
One...two...
하나... 둘...
Come on
어서
what do you want to do
너는 무엇을 하고 싶니?
come with me
나와 함께 가자
Wait a minute...
잠깐만요...
I was shocked. You asked for a beating.
나는 충격을 받았습니다. 당신은 구타를 요청했습니다.
Really sit down
정말로 앉다
sit down for me
나를 위해 앉아주세요
Alas...
아아...
You little bastard, let go now
이 새끼야 이제 놔
Really
정말로
This woman is really...
이 여자는 정말...
Hey, show some respect to others
야, 다른 사람한테도 예의를 좀 보여줘
OK
알았어
sorry
미안
Did you say sorry to me?
나한테 미안하다고 했어?
Okay, let's go
알았어, 가자
OK
알았어
please follow us
우리를 팔로우해주세요
Which guy is it? How dare you come to the sacred set to cause trouble...
어떤 사람이에요? 감히 신성한 세트장에 와서 문제를 일으키다니...
No, you can't take her away
아니, 그녀를 데려갈 수는 없어
uncle
삼촌
No…
아니…
Dingchen…
딩첸…
Li Douxue
리두수에
long time no see
오랜만이네
why are you here
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Dingchen, what are you doing?
딩첸, 뭐해?
leave quickly
빨리 떠나라
Get out of here
여기서 나가세요
Brother, I'm sorry to interrupt you.
형님, 방해해서 미안해요.
We need to take Song Yanzhu away as soon as possible
최대한 빨리 송옌주를 데려가야 해요
The crew gave countless instructions and warnings I must finish filming the daytime scene today
제작진은 셀 수 없이 많은 지시와 경고를 했다. 오늘은 낮신 촬영을 끝내야지
Are you a gangster?
당신은 갱스터입니까?
What hooligan
무슨 훌리건인가
This lady, you are so nice to talk to.
이 아줌마, 얘기하기 너무 좋은데요.
Xuanyu
쉬안위
You go back first
너 먼저 돌아가
I asked you if you are a gangster
조폭이냐고 물었더니
Yes
예
You avoided me when I visited the prison Then come out and become a gangster after being released from prison?
내가 감옥에 갈 때 당신은 나를 피했습니다 그러다가 감옥에서 풀려나서 갱스터가 되는 건가요?
I didn't hide from you
난 너한테 숨지 않았어
But I'm in jail because of you
그런데 너 때문에 내가 감옥에 갇혔어
If it were you, would you want to see me?
만약 당신이라면 나를 보고 싶나요?
Do you really feel...
정말 느껴지시나요...
Did I put you in jail?
내가 당신을 감옥에 넣었나요?
Also, I also live my life very seriously.
또한, 나는 또한 내 인생을 매우 진지하게 살고 있습니다.
A thief who steals and robs all day long Are you also living a serious life?
하루 종일 도둑질하고 훔치는 도둑 당신도 진지한 삶을 살고 있나요?
in this society The little thief who steals a wallet will be looked down upon
이 사회에서 지갑을 훔친 작은 도둑은 무시당할 것이다
But the thief who stole the entire country But it will make people afraid of three points
그런데 나라 전체를 훔친 도둑 하지만 사람들은 세 가지 점을 두려워하게 될 것입니다.
you are absolutely crazy
너 완전 미쳤어
Wrong
틀렸어
The me you knew before was the crazy one
네가 예전에 알던 나는 미친 놈이었어
I thought I just needed to study hard Be filial to your parents and loyal to your country
공부만 열심히 하면 될 줄 알았는데 부모에게 효도하고 나라에 충성하라
can live a good life
좋은 삶을 살 수 있다
It's really ridiculous to think like this
이런 생각을 하는 게 정말 웃긴다.
in this ugly world
이 추악한 세상에서
Living a domineering life is the truth
지배적인 삶을 사는 것이 진리이다
Li Douxue, are you really...
리두수, 정말...?
Became a scumbag
쓰레기가 되었어요
Scumbag?
쓰레기?
Yes
예
Hope the self-proclaimed theater daughter
자칭 연극딸이길 바라
You will never see a scum like me again in the future.
앞으로는 나 같은 쓰레기를 다시는 볼 수 없을 것이다.
Hey, everyone retreat
야 다들 퇴각해라
Okay big brother
알았어 형
You drink slowly
천천히 마셔요
I didn't expect you to come to me
네가 나한테 올 줄은 몰랐어
Have you adapted to life in Seoul?
서울생활에 적응하셨나요?
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
Let me ask you, are you in contact with Douxue?
혹시 Douxue와 연락하고 계시나요?
Well, we are good brothers
뭐, 우리는 좋은 형제야
As a good brother
좋은 동생으로서
How could you let him go and become a gangster?
어떻게 그를 놓아주고 갱스터가 될 수 있습니까?
have you seen him
그 사람 봤어?
That's right
그렇죠
He stormed into our set He met me when he wanted to kidnap the actor.
그 사람이 우리 세트장에 들이닥쳤어 그 사람은 그 배우를 납치하려고 했을 때 나를 만났어요.
I really envy you for having a rogue brother
불량배 동생이 있어서 정말 부럽다
He is not a child anymore
그는 더 이상 어린아이가 아니다
How could you possibly listen to me?
어떻게 내 말을 들을 수 있니?
I think...that's probably his life.
내 생각엔... 그게 아마 그의 삶일 거야.
His life...
그의 인생...
Children of your working parents Are you born to be a gangster?
맞벌이 부모의 자녀 당신은 갱스터가 되기 위해 태어났나요?
Do people with criminal records have to become gangsters?
범죄기록이 있는 사람은 반드시 조폭이 되어야 하는가?
Even if others point fingers at him At least you...
남들이 그에게 손가락질을 해도 적어도 당신은...
You shouldn't have done that to him, bad guy.
그 사람한테 그런 짓은 하지 말았어야지, 나쁜 놈아.
No one's fate is destined by birth
사람의 운명은 태어날 때부터 정해져 있지 않다
Really…
정말…
Li Douxue, are you really...
리두수, 정말...?
Became a scumbag
쓰레기가 되었어요
are you okay
괜찮아?
So why did you drink so much?
그럼 왜 그렇게 술을 많이 마셨나요?
Tetsuo
테츠오
I have something to ask you
물어볼 게 있어요
Please...
제발...
Let Douxue get out of there
Douxue가 거기서 나가도록 해주세요
Don't let him continue to be a gangster
그 사람이 계속 갱스터가 되도록 놔두지 마세요
Only you can help him now
이제 당신만이 그를 도울 수 있어요
If he was allowed to live like that...
만약 그 사람이 그렇게 살 수 있게 된다면...
He is too pitiful
그 사람이 너무 불쌍해요
Douxue is really pitiful
더쿠 진짜 불쌍하다
Dingchen
딩첸
Now that things have happened, can't you forget him?
이제 그런 일이 일어났으니 그 사람을 잊을 수 없나요?
Tetsuo, I have something to ask you
테츠오, 물어볼 게 있어요
Tell me honestly
솔직하게 말해봐
You ask
당신은 묻는다
Back then…
그때는…
Did Douxue really kill someone?
Douxue가 정말 사람을 죽였나요?
no matter what i think I don't even think he would do that kind of thing
내가 어떻게 생각하든 상관없어 그 사람이 그런 짓을 할 거라고는 생각도 안 해
That's right, Brother Douxue did it.
그렇습니다. Douxue 형제가 해냈습니다.
He went to take revenge on the guy who hit me
그 사람은 나를 때린 사람에게 복수하러 갔어요
Then he got into trouble
그러다가 그 사람이 곤경에 빠졌어요
His life is really rough
그 사람 인생은 정말 험난해요
God, is this going too far?
맙소사, 너무 멀리 가는 건가요?
Why are you so cruel to poor people?
왜 가난한 사람들에게 그렇게 잔인합니까?
So painful
너무 고통스러워
Oh my God, how much did you drink?
맙소사, 얼마나 마셨나요?
I still smell of alcohol all over my body.
아직도 온 몸에서 술 냄새가 난다.
What is this? Is it hangover soup?
이게 뭔가요? Is it hangover soup?
You are truly my good friend
당신은 정말 나의 좋은 친구예요
Ouch, my stomach feels so uncomfortable
아, 배가 너무 불편해요
Stinky girl, you really make me jealous
냄새나는 여자야 넌 정말 날 질투나게 해
And a black knight I'll carry you home drunk
And a black knight 술에 취해 집까지 데려다줄게
Who?
누구?
Don't you remember?
기억하지 못하시나요?
It was Tetsuo who sent you back
널 돌려보낸 건 테츠오였어
Tetsuo?
Tetsuo?
Did you really drink until you lost your memory? Still pretending to be stupid
정말 기억을 잃을 때까지 술을 마셨나요? 아직도 바보인 척
How could he carry me back?
그 사람이 어떻게 나를 다시 데리고 갈 수 있었을까?
This was the first time I saw him after graduating from high school
고등학교 졸업 후 처음 봤어요.
He has become so handsome
그 사람 너무 멋있어졌어
When did you resume contact?
언제 다시 연락하셨나요?
That's not the point now...
지금 그게 중요한게 아니잖아...
Where is my watch?
Where is my watch?
What time is it now?
지금은 몇시입니까?
I'm late...
I'm late...
what to do
무엇을 해야할지
Hey, I've already cooked for you
야, 난 이미 널 위해 요리를 했어
Let’s go out after eating
밥 먹고 나가자
No, I don't have time
No, I don't have time
(Waterfall Nightclub)
(Waterfall Nightclub)
Big brother… Really
Big brother… 정말로
You little crew cut
너네 크루 컷
My hair just won't grow long What else can I do
머리가 길지 않을 것 같아요 내가 또 무엇을 할 수 있나요
he is my guest
그 사람은 내 손님이야
So…
그래서…
Are you here to persuade me not to join the underworld?
저를 지하세계에 들어가지 말라고 설득하러 오신 겁니까?
No, how am I qualified to advise you?
아니, 내가 어떻게 당신에게 조언할 자격이 있나요?
I'm a scumbag too
나도 쓰레기야
Just Dingchen she...
그냥 딩첸 그녀...
I still can't seem to forget you
난 아직도 당신을 잊지 못하는 것 같아요
she cried a lot
그 사람은 많이 울었어
It seems she thinks I'm very pitiful
그 사람은 내가 너무 불쌍하다고 생각하는 것 같아
That's not necessarily the reason, right?
반드시 그런 이유는 아니겠죠?
While you're in jail
당신이 감옥에 있는 동안
She will write to you regularly
그녀는 정기적으로 당신에게 편지를 보낼 것입니다
I often visit you too
나도 자주 찾아오는데
But how could you break up?
그런데 어떻게 헤어질 수 있었나요?
Because I feel like a loser
왜냐면 내가 패배자처럼 느껴지거든
Just take the initiative to break up
그냥 솔선해서 헤어지자
Stop talking about this
이 얘기는 그만둬
Memories of childhood love are too childish
어릴적 사랑의 추억은 너무 유치해
Brother
형제
Do I have to be a prosecutor?
검사가 되어야 합니까?
Right. You want to be a prosecutor before you graduate.
오른쪽. 당신은 졸업하기 전에 검사가 되고 싶어합니다.
So be it, I will fulfill your wish
그럼 됐어, 소원을 들어줄게
You can also fulfill my wish
당신도 내 소원을 들어줄 수 있어요
I now...
나는 지금...
You should be able to date Dingchen.
Dingchen과 데이트할 수 있어야 합니다.
Tetsuo
테츠오
Dingchen has nothing to do with me anymore
딩첸은 이제 나랑 아무 상관 없어
Really?
정말
Do you really mean what you said?
정말로 당신이 말한 것이 진심인가요?
But...even so, don't date her
하지만...그래도 그 사람과 데이트하지 마세요
Didn't you say you have nothing to do with her?
당신은 그 사람과 아무 관계도 없다고 하지 않았나요?
Then why not
그렇다면 왜 안되겠습니까?
You just said it yourself
방금 직접 말했잖아
You are also a scumbag
너도 쓰레기야
Even if I miss my old love
옛 사랑이 그리워도
Dingchen shouldn’t associate with scum like us.
Dingchen은 우리 같은 쓰레기와 어울리면 안됩니다.
Isn't it?
그렇지 않나요?
You are the one who made me become a scumbag
나를 쓰레기로 만든 건 너야
what did you say
뭐라고 하셨나요
Don't think you are the only victim
당신이 유일한 피해자라고 생각하지 마세요
From that incident to now I don’t live a day of ease either.
그 사건 이후 지금까지 나도 편안한 하루를 살지 않습니다.
So just give up on Dingchen
그러니까 그냥 딩첸 포기해
Do you want to tell her the truth?
그녀에게 진실을 말하고 싶나요?
In fact, I killed the person
사실 내가 사람을 죽였어
if you don't want to do this What's the problem?
당신이 이것을하고 싶지 않다면 무엇이 문제인가요?
Why can't I date her?
나는 왜 그녀와 데이트할 수 없나요?
Just think of Dingchen being by your side
그냥 Dingchen이 네 옆에 있다고 생각해봐
with contemptuous eyes Look at me becoming a gangster
경멸하는 눈으로 갱스터가 되어가는 나를 봐
Just imagining it makes me feel disgusted.
상상만 해도 역겨운 기분이 듭니다.
Do you think you gave me everything?
당신이 나에게 모든 것을 주었다고 생각합니까?
Don't get me wrong
오해하지 마세요
You never considered me a real brother
당신은 나를 진짜 형제라고 생각한 적이 없습니다
Because you can't get Dingchen's heart
딩첸의 마음을 얻을 수 없으니까
Do you want me not to date her?
내가 그 사람과 데이트하지 않기를 바라나요?
What nonsense is this?
이게 무슨 말도 안되는 소리입니까?
Since we're both bastards
우리 둘 다 개자식이니까
There's no reason among the bastards to begin with.
애초에 개자식들 사이에는 이유가 없습니다.
What else do you expect?
또 무엇을 기대합니까?
(O’s apartment)
(O의 아파트)
(China Film Distribution Company)
(중국영화배급회사)
Are you interested in China Film Distribution Company?
중국영화배급회사에 관심이 있으신가요?
That boss Luo is a famous gambler.
그 보스 Luo는 유명한 도박꾼입니다.
I don't know if he is Being entangled by those crooks in the gambling world
그 사람인지는 모르겠지만 도박계의 그 사기꾼들에게 얽혀
I heard that he has been in a difficult situation recently
최근 힘든 상황에 처해있다고 들었는데
(Namdo Film Company Seoul Branch Boss Wu Dingchen)
(남도영화사 서울지점) 우딩첸 상사)
Are you working under boss Che Jinyu?
최진위 상사 밑에서 일하시나요?
Yes
예
Of course I know the character Boss Che.
물론 나는 보스 체라는 캐릭터를 알고 있다.
What's the matter with her sending you to me?
그녀가 당신을 나에게 보낸 게 무슨 문제인가요?
Our boss wants to partner with you
우리 상사는 당신과 협력하고 싶어합니다
(Boss Luo Rishun)
(뤄리슌 사장)
She wants to partner with me Do you do film distribution in the Jeolla-do area?
그녀는 나와 파트너가 되고 싶어해 전라도 지역에서는 영화 배급을 하시나요?
No, she hopes to partner with you Do film distribution in Jingjiang area
아니요, 그녀는 당신과 파트너가 되기를 원합니다 Jingjiang 지역에서 영화 배급
what
뭐
People say she is a strong woman
사람들은 그녀가 강한 여자라고 말해요
I didn't expect she was so brave
나는 그녀가 그렇게 용감할 줄은 몰랐다
Boss Luo, please continue to run the company
루오 상사님, 회사를 계속 운영해주세요
Our boss wants to take 30% of the shares
우리 상사는 주식의 30%를 갖고 싶어한다
Listen carefully
잘 들어라
This circle is more exclusive than the underworld.
이 서클은 지하 세계보다 더 배타적입니다.
If you invade other people's territory casually,
남의 영역을 함부로 침범하면
If you are not careful, you will die miserably.
조심하지 않으면 비참하게 죽을 것입니다.
Go back and tell your boss
돌아가서 상사에게 말하세요
If you want to enjoy your old age
노후를 즐기고 싶다면
Just stay in Gwangju
그냥 광주에 있어라
OK
알았어
Right
오른쪽
It seems that your gambling money is almost spent.
도박으로 돈을 거의 다 쓴 것 같습니다.
Our boss doesn't know you are gambling
우리 상사는 당신이 도박을 하고 있다는 것을 모른다
I originally wanted to object to her seeking a partnership with you.
나는 원래 그녀가 당신과 파트너십을 맺는 것을 반대하고 싶었습니다.
But tell her about your gambling I'm afraid of ruining the relationship between the two of you
하지만 그녀에게 당신의 도박에 대해 말해주세요 두 사람의 관계가 망가질까봐 두렵다.
That’s why I came to visit you
그래서 내가 당신을 만나러 왔어요
Thank you very much for your rejection
거절해주셔서 정말 감사합니다.
Wait
잠깐
30% of the shares?
지분이 30%?
How much do you want to subscribe for?
얼마를 구독하시겠습니까?
so
그래서
The other party offered 100 million won
상대방이 1억원을 제안했다.
A bit expensive
조금 비싸다
But compared with the development of subsequent market expansion, This little money is nothing, right?
그러나 후속 시장 확장의 발전과 비교하면, 이 작은 돈은 아무것도 아니죠?
Didn’t you say that Boss Luo has conditions?
루오 보스에게 조건이 있다고 하지 않았나요?
First, he asked for a partnership Absolutely keep it secret
먼저 파트너십을 요청했다. 절대 비밀로 해주세요
Of course
물론이다
If the news gets out It is difficult to gain a foothold in the Jingjiang area
그 소식이 전해지면 Jingjiang 지역에서는 거점을 확보하기가 어렵습니다.
There's more
더 있어요
He said that as long as he had money, he would buy back the shares
그는 돈만 있으면 주식을 되사겠다고 말했다.
We have to sell to him anytime
우리는 언제든지 그 사람에게 팔아야 해요
how is this
이건 어때?
Wouldn't it be a waste of time for us to do this?
우리가 이런 일을 하는 것은 시간 낭비가 아닌가?
If he returns the principal to us We can't even get dividends
만약 그 사람이 우리에게 원금을 돌려준다면 배당도 못 받아
Boss, this is definitely a loss-making business.
사장님, 이건 확실히 손실이 나는 사업이에요.
so
그래서
I will agree to his conditions
나는 그의 조건에 동의할 것이다
are you crazy
너 미쳤어?
you idiot
바보야
you did a great job
당신은 훌륭한 일을 했어요
Boss…
보스…
Do you want to catch up with Dingchen’s taillights? It will take hundreds of years
딩첸의 미등을 따라잡고 싶으신가요? 수백년은 걸릴거야
Have you ever heard of a gambler paying back his money?
도박꾼이 돈을 갚았다는 이야기를 들어본 적이 있나요?
Have you ever heard of a gambler borrowing money?
도박꾼이 돈을 빌리는 이야기를 들어본 적이 있나요?
That's the truth...
그게 진실이에요...
(passbook) There are fully 300 million people here
(통장) 여기에는 완전히 3억 명의 사람들이 있습니다.
Try to get the middle part
중간 부분을 얻으려고 노력하십시오.
Oh my god
맙소사
You said you would give me company shares?
나한테 회사 주식을 주겠다고 했었지?
How much do you plan to give me?
나에게 얼마를 주려고 합니까?
don't you trust me
나를 믿지 않니?
Boss, do you trust me?
사장님, 저를 믿으시나요?
Okay, tell me how much you want
알았어, 얼마를 원하는지 말해봐
If I get the middle part
중간 부분을 얻으면
Market share of film distribution in Jingjiang region If it reaches 50%
징장 지역 영화 배급 시장 점유율 50%에 도달하면
Please give me 30% of the shares
주식 30%만 주세요
Oh my God, is this girl crazy?
맙소사, 이 여자 미친 건가?
Is your brain abnormal?
뇌가 비정상인가요?
What if it fails?
실패하면 어떻게 되나요?
Then I am willing to work under the boss for the rest of my life.
그러면 나는 남은 생애 동안 상사 밑에서 일할 의향이 있습니다.
let me think about it
생각해볼게
Insider?
내부자?
We are all called intelligence agents
우리는 모두 정보요원이라 불린다
But most people say he is a mole
하지만 대부분의 사람들은 그가 두더지라고 말합니다.
Is Tetsuo really doing something so dangerous?
테츠오가 정말 그렇게 위험한 짓을 하고 있는 걸까요?
Who on earth asked him to do such a thing?
도대체 누가 그에게 그런 일을 하라고 한 걸까요?
This is it
이것이다
Based on the results of the written report It was Tetsuo who volunteered to take charge after he was discharged from the army early.
서면보고서 결과를 토대로 일찍 군대에서 제대하고 책임을 맡겠다고 자원한 테츠오였다.
Times have changed recently
최근에는 시대가 바뀌었어요
Government agencies will not force You can't force people to do this kind of thing
정부기관은 강제하지 않을 것 사람들에게 이런 일을 하도록 강요할 수는 없습니다
How did this come to light?
이것이 어떻게 밝혀졌습니까?
Students in the student movement circle noticed that his whereabouts were suspicious
학생운동계 학생들은 그의 행방이 수상하다는 사실을 알아차렸다.
I took him to school to force him to confess.
나는 그에게 자백을 강요하기 위해 그를 학교에 데려갔습니다.
However
그러나
Tetsuo has made a good friend
테츠오는 좋은 친구를 사귀었어요
Is it called Li Douxue?
리두수(Li Douxue)라고 하나요?
He faced a large group of students alone Rescued Tetsuo
그는 혼자서 많은 학생들과 마주했다 구출된 테츠오
After Tetsuo I should no longer be able to participate in student movements.
테츠오 이후 나는 더 이상 학생운동에 참여할 수 없습니다.
He just needs to prepare well for the judicial examination
사법시험만 잘 준비하면 된다
there won't be any problem
아무 문제 없을 거야
Just be low-key
그냥 조용히 지내세요
(1 year later)
(1년 후)
Douxue, thank you for your hard work
Douxue님, 노고에 감사드립니다
Sales volume has been maintained at a certain level.
판매량은 일정 수준을 유지하고 있습니다.
The point is, no one will come to make trouble if nothing happens. Really good
요점은 아무 일도 일어나지 않으면 아무도 문제를 일으키지 않을 것이라는 것입니다. 정말 좋아요
Thanks for the compliment, brother
칭찬 고마워요 형님
Shareholders are not happy
주주들은 행복하지 않다
Yongpil, you have to work harder
용필아 더 열심히 해야지
Sorry, bro
미안해요, 형
Also
또한
You are still in the hotel cafe Would you like some soup and rice?
넌 아직 호텔 카페야 국과 밥 좀 드실래요?
what
뭐
You might as well open a soup restaurant.
수프 레스토랑을 여는 것이 나을 수도 있습니다.
Yongpil, please use your head.
용필아, 머리 좀 써라.
Big brother
형님
Why don't you let me run it? What do you think of his nightclubs and restaurants?
내가 운영하게 놔두지 그래? 그의 나이트클럽과 레스토랑에 대해 어떻게 생각하시나요?
You bastard
이 새끼야
Do you want to die in my hands?
내 손에 죽고 싶냐?
Yongpil, I mean...
용필아 내 말은...
Shut up or I'll tear your mouth apart
닥쳐 안 그러면 네 입을 찢어버릴 거야
You rude brat
무례한 놈아
Get out of here
여기서 나가세요
go out
나가다
Really
정말로
Same for you
너도 마찬가지야
How could you say that?
어떻게 그런 말을 할 수 있니?
If you take charge of Yongpil's territory Does he want the people under him to drink the northwest wind?
용필의 영토를 맡는다면 그는 자신의 밑에 있는 사람들이 북서풍을 마시기를 원합니까?
Brother, it's not like that
형님 그런거 아니예요
I want him to manage it My nightclub and restaurant
그 사람이 관리해줬으면 좋겠어 나의 나이트클럽과 레스토랑
what did you say
뭐라고 했어?
I'm on my turf Established a complete management system
난 내 영역에 있어 완벽한 관리 시스템 구축
It would be easy if Yong Pil takes over
용필이 인수하면 쉬울텐데
I want to improve the area that Yong-pil is responsible for.
용필이 담당하는 부분을 개선하고 싶다.
Let both sides stabilize
양쪽이 안정되게 해주세요
So
그래서
Do you mean you want to switch territories with him?
그 사람과 영역을 바꾸고 싶다는 뜻인가요?
yes
응
I really can't stand that guy I didn’t even finish listening to what I said…
그 사람 정말 못 참겠어 내 말을 다 듣지도 않았는데…
Brother, we are a family
형님, 우리는 가족이에요
(Judicial trainee appointment ceremony)
(사법연수생 임명식)
Tetsuo
테츠오
Dingchen
딩첸
Prospective prosecutor, congratulations.
예비검사님, 축하드립니다.
thank you
감사합니다
Thank you for your hard work
당신의 노고에 감사드립니다
Tetsuo
테츠오
Mom
엄마
Mom can die without regrets now
엄마는 이제 후회 없이 죽어도 돼
Don't cry. Today is a great day.
울지 마세요. 오늘은 좋은 날입니다.
Well...I shouldn't cry
음... 울면 안 되는데
If only your dad could see you like this How nice it would be
아빠가 널 이렇게 볼 수만 있다면 얼마나 좋을까
I will go to my father’s grave again later
나중에 다시 아버지 무덤에 가겠습니다.
I haven't seen him for a long time
나는 그를 오랫동안 보지 못했어요
Yes, you should go and see it too
응 너도 가서 봐야지
You have to thank uncle
삼촌에게 감사해야 해
He often helps organize your father's grave.
그는 종종 아버지의 무덤 정리를 돕습니다.
Uncle, thank you very much
삼촌, 정말 고마워요
Don't say that. This is what I should do.
그렇게 말하지 마세요. 이것이 내가 해야 할 일이다.
You are truly amazing…
당신은 정말 대단해요…
You gave the Cui family a comeback
Cui 가족에게 컴백을 선사하셨습니다.
This is all thanks to your help
이게 다 네 도움 덕분이야
What did I do...
내가 무슨 짓을 한 거지...
Aunt, why are you crying?
이모, 왜 울어요?
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
여러분의 노고에 감사드립니다. 여러분의 노고에 감사드립니다.
You two can sleep at my house for one night and then go back.
너희 둘은 우리 집에서 하룻밤 자고 돌아가면 돼.
Let me buy you two a drink
둘이서 한잔 사줄게
No need…
필요없어…
We have to go back quickly
우리 빨리 돌아가야 해
Things in the fields are piling up like a mountain
들판에 있는 것들이 산더미처럼 쌓여 있어요
I'm too lazy to talk about him
너무 게으른 나머지 그 사람에 대해 이야기할 수가 없어
Before this guy came up to Seoul
이 사람이 서울에 오기 전에
Still insisting on growing vegetables on a small field
아직도 작은 밭에서 채소 재배를 고집하고 있어요
But it’s okay if I sleep one night and then leave.
하지만 하룻밤 자고 나가면 괜찮아요.
This old woman...
이 늙은 여자...
You have a lot to do
당신은 할 일이 많다
Uncle hasn't changed at all
삼촌은 전혀 변하지 않았어
Tetsuo, you don’t have to worry about us
테츠오, 우리 걱정은 하지 않아도 돼
Mom is going back first
엄마가 먼저 돌아갈게
OK
알았어
Let's go
가자
Then I'll find you later
그럼 나중에 찾아갈게
good
좋아
you are amazing
당신은 정말 대단해요
Be careful on the road
길에서 조심하세요
What's going on? Will anyone else come?
무슨 일이야? 다른 사람도 올까요?
what
뭐
No more
더 이상은 안돼
congratulations
축하합니다
Tetsuo passed the exam in no time
테츠오는 단숨에 시험에 합격했다
Who did he inherit his intelligence from?
그는 누구로부터 지능을 물려받았습니까?
Is it mom or dad?
엄마야, 아빠야?
It must be mom
엄마여야만 해
I think so
나는 그렇게 생각한다
Brother Zhongzhong, I have something to ask you.
중중 형제님, 묻고 싶은 것이 있습니다.
Just tell me what it is
그게 뭔지 말해봐
Tetsuo wants to be a prosecutor
테츠오는 검사가 되고 싶어
Please give him a helping hand
그에게 도움의 손길을 주세요
His judicial examination results Isn't it among the best?
그의 사법심사 결과 최고 중 하나 아닌가요?
But I heard from our store The wife of the Minister of Justice said
그런데 저희 가게에서 들었어요 법무부장관 부인이 말했다.
If you have participated in the student movement It is impossible to become a judge or prosecutor...
학생운동에 참여한 적이 있는 경우 판사나 검사가 되는 건 불가능하다..
Yes, then Tetsuo can only become a lawyer.
네, 그렇다면 테츠오는 변호사만 될 수 있어요.
There's nothing I can do about it
내가 할 수 있는 일은 아무것도 없어
And honestly
그리고 솔직히
If it were revealed that he had been an intelligence agent It's even more troublesome
만약 그가 정보요원이었다는 사실이 밝혀졌다면 더욱 곤란해요
Then he should be made a prosecutor.
그러면 그 사람을 검사로 만들어야 한다.
He has been working quietly for the country...
조용히 나라를 위해 일하시네요...
This thing is difficult
이 일이 어렵다
You'll know just by looking at the records
기록만 봐도 알겠지만
He didn't provide it at all Information about student activists
그는 그것을 전혀 제공하지 않았습니다 학생 활동가에 대한 정보
It means that he is just following the trend to please both sides.
이는 그가 양쪽 모두를 만족시키기 위해 추세를 따르고 있다는 것을 의미합니다.
That's a gray area where there's nothing black or white
그곳은 검은색도 흰색도 없는 회색지대입니다.
he wants to be a prosecutor
그 사람은 검사가 되고 싶어해
This is also my wish
This is also my wish
If he had cooperated with intelligence agencies at that time
만약 당시 정보기관과 협력했다면
I can still push him Make him an elite prosecutor
I can still push him 엘리트 검사로 만들어주세요
I don’t even know what the current situation is.
현재 상황이 어떤지조차 모르겠습니다.
His mind is as smart as his mother's
그의 마음은 그의 어머니만큼 똑똑하다
But just like his father Hold on to a worthless conscience
But just like his father 쓸모없는 양심을 붙잡아라
Yes
예
He looks a lot like his dad
그 사람은 그의 아버지와 많이 닮았어요
Tetsuo and his biological father Just like they were carved from the same mold
테츠오와 그의 친아버지 마치 같은 틀에서 조각된 것처럼
He is very ambitious
He is very ambitious
he wants power
he wants power
Now that we are here You should at least meet me before leaving.
Now that we are here 적어도 떠나기 전에 나를 만나야 해요.
Why did you just leave immediately?
왜 바로 떠나셨나요?
Thank you for your hard work
당신의 노고에 감사드립니다
Take this to catch up with friends
친구들과 연락하려면 이걸 가져가세요
what is this
이게 뭐야?
Oh my god
맙소사
Li Douxue becomes the second person in Guangzhuo Gang Be very generous when you take action
Li Douxue는 Guangzhuo Gang의 두 번째 인물이 되었습니다. 행동을 취할 때 매우 관대하게 행동하라
So handsome
너무 잘생겼어
I have fulfilled your order now, right?
이제 귀하의 주문을 이행했습니다. 그렇죠?
Don't be too arrogant
Don't be too arrogant
Now you are just qualified to repay your kindness The main event starts now
이제 당신은 은혜에 보답할 자격이 생겼습니다 이제 메인 이벤트가 시작됩니다
Yeah, this is just the beginning, right?
응, 이건 시작에 불과하지?
But there's one more thing I also plan to take action
그런데 한 가지가 더 있어요 나도 조치를 취할 계획이다.
Dingchen…
딩첸…
I will make her my woman
나는 그녀를 내 여자로 만들 것이다
I never expected that my son would be right in front of me
내 아들이 바로 내 앞에 있을 거라고는 전혀 예상하지 못했어요
The dull father couldn't recognize him
둔한 아버지는 그를 알아보지 못했다
Please help Tetsuo Let him be the prosecutor
도와주세요 테츠오 그 사람이 검사가 되게 해주세요
You are his father
당신은 그의 아버지입니다
Stop pretending you're a bad person
나쁜 사람인 척은 그만둬
I know you still can't forget her
나는 당신이 아직도 그녀를 잊지 못한다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
if you want
당신이 원한다면
Let's compete again like we did in high school.
고등학교 때처럼 다시 경쟁하자.
fair and just
공평하고 정당하다
ok
좋아요
You brat...
이 녀석...
(Oasis)
(오아시스)
Is there no other reason?
다른 이유는 없나요?
Why can Brother Douxue do it but I can’t?
Douxue 형제는 할 수 있는데 왜 나는 할 수 없나요?
(fight) I'm not afraid at all
(싸움) 전혀 두렵지 않아요
why
왜
Because I do all this to fight for human rights.
나는 인권을 위해 싸우기 위해 이 모든 일을 하고 있기 때문이다.
Just hit me like you always do
언제나처럼 그냥 때려줘
car boss
자동차 상사
Boss, you are the best
사장님, 당신이 최고예요
I'm no longer the puppet I used to be
나는 더 이상 예전의 꼭두각시가 아니다
I am Choi Cheol-woong, a prosecutor of the Republic of Korea.
저는 대한민국 검사 최철웅입니다.
I don't understand why he is so nice to him
그 사람이 왜 그렇게 친절하게 대하는지 이해가 안 돼요
Dingchen...she was kidnapped
딩첸... 납치됐어
if you want to help You should be able to find a way
당신이 돕고 싶다면 방법을 찾을 수 있어야 합니다.